It's as if you've worked a long day in your life, you've worked a long day and then
C 'est  comme  si  tu  avais  travaill횄짤  une  grande  journ횄짤e  de  ta  vie,  tu  as  travaill횄짤  une  grande  journ횄짤e  et  puis
you come home, you can take off your shoes, you
tu  rentres  횄혻  la  maison,  tu  peux  enlever  tes  chaussures,  tu
can sit in your armchair with a good beer,
peux  te  mettre  dans  ton  fauteuil  avec  une  bonne  bi횄짢re,
it's a stage for you, where you are happy
c 'est  un  stade  횄혻  toi,  o횄쨔  tu  es  content
with the work you've done, for once you're happy, you say to yourself, "There, a big job
du  travail  que  tu  as  fait,  pour  une  fois  tu  es  content,  tu  te  dis  tiens  voil횄혻,  un  gros  travail
has been done."
qui  a  횄짤t횄짤  fait.
You're sitting there, you're resting a little, you're resting your body a little,
Tu  es  assis  l횄혻,  tu  te  reposes  un  peu,  tu  reposes  le  corps  un  peu,
and then you rest your mind a little.
et  puis  tu  reposes  un  peu  l 'esprit.
You develop a small quality in your mind.
Tu d횄짤veloppes dans ton esprit une petite qualit횄짤.
You light this small flame that I'm going to suggest you light,
Tu allumes cette petite flamme que je vais vous proposer d'allumer,
which is a small flame that should try to remind you of contentment.
qui  est  une  petite  flamme  qui  doit  essayer  de  vous  rappeler  le  contentement.
To learn to...
Apprendre 횄혻...
instant, to appreciate what we have.
instant, 횄혻 appr횄짤cier ce qu'on a.
We're off to the skull.
On est parti pour le cr횄짖ne.